In this special segment of ours,
Akshay Bhagwat of Gem Financial has
joined us with his Option Streets.
Akshay, good afternoon, tell us which
stock is in today's market and what will be your option strategy.
Good afternoon,
and today for the first time in intraday, Bank Nifty is making a good pick-up
and sustaining above 45000.
So, we would like to recommend State Bank of
India in options. The
current rate of State Bank is 594.
It has a strong resistance point of 600
because
pressure is being seen from both sides again and again. But the way the
options are moving at 600 tomorrow,
we are seeing significant unweeding at the 600 strike yesterday.
And we believe that
you will get to see this breakout soon, where you
can see State Bank at the level of 615 to 620. If you participate in this through options, then
we would recommend
buying at 600 tomorrow,
whose premium is around  It is trading between 7 to 7:30 rupees,
right now its target will be
first target ₹11 and second target 14 and
you can proceed with this trade by making a stoppage of ₹3,
your contract is of 27th July, that is
till monthly expiry, here the strategy is to
buy it tomorrow, you will get it in the range of 6 to ₹7,
first target
11, second target 14 and
you have to place Star Plus here for three
but this is a strong option strategy
which is on SBI